1992年 夏天
汤米
Tommy?
汤米 你醒着吗
Tommy, are you awake?
我看到你弄丢的小船在外面
I saw your missing boat outside.
我去帮你拿回来
I'm gonna get it for you.
萨默斯夫人
Mrs. Summers?
你确定我要走吗
Are you sure I should go?
我可以留下的
I don't mind staying.
不用 没事 你回家吧
No, it's fine. You should go home.
我一会儿去看看孩子
I'll check on the kids later.
好的 萨默斯夫人
Okay, Mrs. Summers.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
找到了
There you are.
丽贝卡
Rebecca?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
抱歉 妈妈
Sorry, Mom.
我不是故…
I didn't mean...
妈
Mom?
塔玛戈米 塔玛戈米
Temagami. Temagami.
Temagami. Temagami...
妈 妈 妈
Mom! Mom! Mom!
救命
Help!
《暗泳》
酿酒人队昨天和马林鱼队打了加时赛
Brewers played extra innings with the Marlins yesterday.
他们打了12局
They fell in 12.
第11局中 界外球掉在了一垒线 而且是二振
Oneone. Foul ball up the first baseline, and it is two strikes.
酿酒人队在本赛季的加时赛中取得8比9的成绩
Brewers are eight and nine in extrainning games so far this season.
希望他们再接再厉
Hoping to keep that streak alive.
雷 他们都准备好了
Ray,  they're ready for us.
爸
Dad.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的 我很好
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
我准备一下 你们先进去吧
Give me a head start. I'll meet you inside.
这里有你要的所有东西
This has got every single thing that you asked for.
有24小时紧急呼叫服务
It has 24hour emergency call service.
好吧 这点很棒
Right? Which is great.
还有单层卧室
It's got sing-lelevel bedrooms.
带浴缸 所有的浴室都有扶手
It's got bath... All the bathrooms have handrails.
这里离双城最好的医疗机构
And you're just minutes away from one of the best
只有几分钟的路程
medical facilities in the Twin Cities.
是啊
Yeah.
当你需要医疗服务时
It's... I mean, it's really kind of perfect lease
这里就是最完美的出租房
for when you just need a little extra help.
你不喜欢吗
Do you not like it?
-这里挺好的  -你是不是在找
Well, it's nice. Are you... Are you looking
可以投球的地方
for a place to throw the ball around?
等你康复了
Is there any chance that you're gonna bring
能不能在这里表演下你的招牌挥棒
that Waller swing here once you get better?
不好意思 我会调查我所有的客户
I'm sorry. I Google all my clients,
不是每天都能遇到一个
and it's just not every day that I get a...
大联盟三垒手
A bigleague third baseman.
是啊 我…
Yeah, no. I, um...
我现在只想安心养病
I'm just focused on getting better now
在家呆一段时间
and spending some time at home
-陪陪家人  -你知道吗
and being with family.  Well, you know what?
你可以花点钱在这个地方
You can spend some of that baseball money right here.
安心是无法用价钱衡量的
You can't put a price on peace of mind.
是啊
Yeah.
但显然这里可以
Yeah, well, apparently, here you can.
是4200块
It's 4,200 bucks.
说笑了
Oh, just...
知道吗 这厨房也不错
You know what? In the kitchen.
我带你们看看
Come here. I want to show you.
有个无障碍设计
There's this accessible design.
我不知道是谁弄的 但我自己也想搞一个
And I don't know who did it, but I think I want one myself.
-只能这么说  -你们喜欢吗
I'll tell you that much. You guys like it or...
-喜欢  -我可能会成为你的邻居
Yeah. I might be your neighbor.
等等 亲爱的
Wait, wait. Honey, honey.
-停车 停车  -什么
Wait, stop, stop.  What?
亲爱的 停车 快看
Honey, stop, stop, stop. Look.
快看
Look. Look.
我本想带你们看看这里
I would've shown you this place,
但这里并不符合你们的要求
but it didn't really meet your checklist.
-而且这不是出租房  -我知道
And this is not a rental, right?  I know.
-我们只是好奇看看  -好的
We were just curious.  Okay.
这里几十年都没换过屋主
Right, well, it's only one owner for the last couple decades.
我想只需要打扫一下就能住了
And, uh, you know, it needs just a little work, I think.
但这个价格不会在市场上卖太久
But it's not gonna be on the market very long at this price.
而且这是挨着哈罗德霍尔特高中的学区房
Oh, and you're in a great school district with Harold Holt.
我秋季开学就去那里
That's where I start in the fall.
真的吗 我也是名自豪的校友
No, really? Oh, I'm a proud alum myself.
加油 湖鳟队
Go, Lake Trout.
你教哪个科目
And what subject do you teach there?
没有 我只是做行政的
Oh, no. I'm just in the admin office
顺便完成我的特殊教育在线学位
while I finish my degree online for special education.
那你挺棒的
Oh. Good for you. Good for you.
追梦永远不晚
Well, it's never too late to follow your dream.
太棒了
Too awesome.
是啊
Yeah.
天啊 这太棒了
Oh, my gosh. This is amazing.
那是什么 水果篮
What is that? The fruit baskets.
雷去哪儿了
Where did Ray get off to?
我没看到他
I didn't see him.
你在这呢
There you are.
嘿
Hey.
有个泳池
There's a pool.
我以前很怕泳池
I used to be scared of pools.
我爸在我三岁时把我推进了本宁堡的一个
My dad pushed me into one of the training tanks
训练水池
at Fort Benning when I was three.
要么沉 要么游
Sink or swim.
我想我选择了游
I guess I swam.
我一直想要个泳池
I always wanted a pool.
我们小时候经常上街
When we were kids, we used to go down the street,
闯进KOA 去游泳
break into the KOA, go swimming.
我们常常假装是郊区的富家子弟
We used to pretend that we were the rich kids from the suburbs.
嘿 妈妈 我们能吃午饭了吗
Hey, Mom, can we get lunch?
我准备好走了 能去吃点东西吗
Yeah, I'm ready to go. Can we get some food?
走吧 爸爸
Come on, old man.
别沉浸在怀旧中
Before we get too nostalgic.
一张熟悉的面孔走向本垒
Familiar face makes his way down to the plate.
这是一个怎样的故事
What a story this has been, folks.
在与病魔抗争了一年后
After a year battling illness,
雷·沃勒想通过大联盟的复出
Ray Waller is trying to do the impossible
来完成不可能的事
with a Major League comeback.
球来势汹汹
Glider inside.
沃勒用力一挥
Waller digs for it...
击中了
and connects!
此球直飞中外场
It's a deep ball into far center field,
消失不见了
and it is gone!
爸
Dad!
妈 快来 爸落水了
Mom, hurry! Dad fell in!
雷 发生了什么 你没事吧
Ray, what happened? Are you okay?
-爸 出什么事了  -没事
Dad? What happened? Yeah.
妈 他没事吧
Mom, is he okay?
-深呼吸 没事的  -我没事
Just breathe. It's okay.   I'm fine.
-妈 他的拐杖  -好的
Mom, his cane.  Yep.
-伊西 帮我一下  -好
Izzy, give me... Help me here.  Yep.
你能行吗
Yeah. You got it?
好的
Okay.
-你可以吗  -可以
You got it? Okay.
-真的吗  -真的 没问题
Yeah? Yeah. Okay.
离你上次晕倒隔了多久
How long has it been since your last episode?
这次不算晕倒
Well, it wasn't really an episode,
我觉得不是 就像…
I don't think. It's like...
大约在六个月前的春训
At spring training about six months ago.
我的建议是将诊断升级为
My recommendation is to escalate the diagnosis
继发进展型多发性硬化症
to secondary progressive MS.
但医生说他的病情稳定了
No, but the doctor said he was stabilizing
只需注意管理问题
and that it's about managing now.
最好有更准确的诊断
It's better to have a more accurate diagnosis.
-你在做物疗吗  -没有
Are you in PT?  No...
我就在前院和孩子们
Um, well, I mean, I'm throwing the ball around
扔一扔棒球而已
in the front yard with the kids, and, like, that.
我们刚通过我的学校拿到了保险
We just got insurance through the school where I'm working.
-是的  -忘了棒球吧
Yeah.  Forget baseball.
目前 我们要找一个低强度的活动
For now, we need to find a lowimpact activity
让你每天都可以做
that you can do every day.
散步 瑜伽
Walking, yoga.
大多数治疗师建议游泳
Most therapists recommend swimming.
我知道你会感觉整个世界
Look, I know it feels like your whole world
都在天翻地覆
is turning upside down.
你们都需要做出牺牲
It's going to take sacrifice from you both,
但你们可以一起建立美好的生活
but you can build a good life together.
首先 你们必须放下旧生活
First, you have to let go of the old one.
接下来的几天 你先使用轮椅过渡
Use the wheelchair for the next few days while you regulate,
下周再过来复诊
and I will bring you back in next week.
亲爱的 如果我们租了那栋别墅
Honey, if we rent that townhome,
就会像住在医院里一样
it'd be like living in a hospital.
我不想再当病秧子
I don't want to be the sick guy anymore.
但你确实病了 雷
But you're sick, Ray.
-我们需要直面这个问题  -我知道 我只是不想
We need to deal with that head-on.  I know. I just don't want it
定义我们现在的生活
to define our whole life now.
另一栋房子怎么样
What about that other house?
孩子们会喜欢的 那么宽敞
The kids will love it, with all that room.
还带了泳池
And with a swimming pool,
我们可以在自家后院进行水疗
we'll have water therapy in our own backyard.
你知道我想要我们自己的房子
You know I want our own place.
我厌倦了孩子们转学
I'm tired of the kids changing schools,
每次转校后都得交新朋友
making new friends every time you get traded.
你知道吗 我希望我们能扎根落户
I want us to put down roots, you know?
我只是想确定这也是你想要的
I just need to know that you want that, too.
我想要
I do.
伊芙
Eve.
我也希望那样
I want that, too.
我保证
I promise.
另外 你知道我还想问什么吗
Also, you know what else I was wondering about?
你那件黑色比基尼还在吗
Do you have that black bikini still?
你知道我说的是哪件吗
You know which one I'm talking about?
-有交叉肩带的那件  -你还在医院呢
With the crisscross straps?  Guy's in a hospital.
脑子里尽想着这些
This is what he's thinking.
嘿 你在这呢 西达
Hey, there you are, Cider.
过来 咪咪
Come here, buddy.
你喜欢我们的新家吗
How do you like our new home?
是不是很棒 屋子很大吧
Isn't it awesome? It's so big, right?
-伊西 回头见  -好的
Izzy, I'll see you later. Okay.
-祝你好运  -谢谢
Good luck.  Thanks.
-你没问题的  -好
You got it.  Yeah.
-等下 等下  -咋啦
Oh, wait, wait, wait.  What?
哦 谢谢
Oh, thanks.
-再见 笨蛋  -再见 白痴
See you later, dipshit. See you, barf bag.
你觉得你今年能上场吗
Think you're gonna go out this year?
能 爸爸说我快到青春期了
Yeah. Dad says I'm about to hit my growth spurt.
慢着 其实吧
Actually, wait.
我觉得你现在就到青春期了
Yeah. I think you're hitting it right now.
等等 我来开门
Here. Wait, wait. I got it.
嘿 你有多高
Hey, how tall are you?
听着…
Look, um...
你能把胳膊举起来吗
Can you just put your arm up real quick?
对 就像这样
Like, yeah. Just like that.
是的 你的臂展很长
Yeah, you have a great wingspan.
谢谢
Thanks.
你周五应该来
You should come on Friday.
-好的  -我叫罗尼
Okay.  My name's Ronin.
哈罗德霍尔特高中
基督游泳俱乐部
为他
而游
周五
选拔时间
下午3-4点
嘿 你周五真的应该来 会很棒的
Hey, you should come on Friday, for real. It's gonna be dope.
你们觉不觉得气味很怪
Does it smell weird to you guys?
不觉得 你只是又变回狗了
Nah, you're just turning back into a dog.
必须把你送回爸妈发现你的收容所
Have to take you back to the shelter where Mom and Dad found you.
PYX106的播放列表是怎么回事
What is with the PYX 106 playlist?
我加了很多经典歌曲
I'm bringing back the classics, babe.
-我喜欢 爸爸  -我…
I like it, Dad. Hey, El, I...
我在迎新会上和你的教练谈过了
I talked with your coach at orientation.
他说如果我去帮助训练 效果会很好
He thought it might be good if I come and help with practice.
我觉得可能会很有趣 对吧
I thought it might be kinda fun, right?
是的 老爸 今年该我上场了吧
Yeah, Dad. This is my year, right?
对
Yeah.
该你了
It is.
我想我会去游泳队
I think I'm going out for the swim team.
真的吗
Ooh! Really?
-真的  -那太好了 伊西
Yeah. That's great, Iz.
你会很有天赋
Yeah, you're gonna be a natural.
那个奖杯球棒 在你出生那天就有了生命
That trophy bat, that came alive the day you were born.
我在海湾打出过一次猛球
I absolutely launched one into the Bay.
砰
Pop!
球飞了
Splash.
那是第九局 我在本垒上
It was the ninth inning, and I was at the plate,
不知怎么地
and I don't know what it was.
我突然浑身充满了力量
Just this sense of strength came over me.
我知道
I knew it.
我随后就明白了
I knew it right then.
是我的伊西…
My Izzy is...
爸
Dad?
-我的天啊  -怎么了
Oh, my gosh. What happened?
雷 你还好吗
Ray? Are you okay?
-我划了好大条口子  -怎么了
God, I sliced it pretty good.  What happened?
-啊  -看上去…
Ah...  Oh, that looks...
天啊
Oh, God.
天呐
Oh, my gosh. Ew.
-这是什么  -我去
What is that? Oh, God.
小心
Be careful.
这正常吗
Is that supposed to happen?
我觉得不正常
I don't think so.
这安全吗
Is it safe?
没有泳池是绝对安全的
No pool is absolutely safe.
你看到那个盖子了吗
But you see that cap?
那是个井口
That's a wellhead.
我从没亲眼见过真正的泉水池
I've never seen an actual spring-fed pool before in person,
但你们接通了地下水
but you're tapped into groundwater.
我说的是隔水层
I'm talking aquiclude.
就是地下含水层
That's some sublevel aquifer shit.
-什么意思  -对 什么意思呢
What does that mean? Yeah, what does that mean?
我正要告诉你
I'm about to tell you what that means.
意思就是自然过滤
That means natural filtration,
地热加温等等
geothermal heating, the whole shebang.
我们会进行消毒 但这些泉水
Yeah, we'll give it a shock, but these spring pools
应该能起到神奇的护肤效果
are supposed to work miracles on your skin.
周围整个地区都有天然泳池
This whole area had natural pools all around.
养生中心 健康水疗中心
Wellness centers, health spas.
好极了 我们真走运
That's great. Lucky us, huh?
是的
Yeah.
很有意思 不是吗
It's funny, isn't it, though?
我是说
I mean...
我们从水里进化而来
We evolved out of the water
我们爬行动物的大脑知道
and some part of our reptilian brain knows
我们不该再呆在水里 但是…
we're not supposed to be there anymore, but...
我想这就是我们想驯服水的原因
I guess that's why we try to tame it so hard.
就像试图征服死亡
It's like trying to conquer death...
哇 当心
Whoa, whoa. Jesus. Be careful.
-你没事吧  -天啊 抱歉
Are you okay?  God, sorry.
我笨手笨脚的
Butterfingers.
真是白痴
What an idiot.
好了 这是你的发票
All right, well, here's your invoice.
我明天再来
I'll come back tomorrow.
下周之前应该就可以用了
You should be set up by next week.
-好的  -太好了 谢谢
Okay.  Great. Thanks.
嘿 基科 收工啦
Hey, Gecko, let's wrap it up.
快点 动起来 宝贝
Come on. Let's boogie, baby.
好了 可以下水了
All right, we're good to go!
准备好没
Ready?
好了
Yeah.
来吧 爸爸 再扔点
Come on, Dad. Throw some more.
等一下 我先做完这些训练
Hold on. I just got to finish these exercises.
你看见了吗
Are you watching this?
水帮我放松了肌肉 太神奇了
The water takes all the strain off my muscles. It's amazing.
肌肉给我捏捏
Give me those muscles.
都在下面
They're all down there.
我要一口气全部拿完
I'll get 'em all in one breath.
当然 有何不可 上
Yeah, sure. Why not? Go.
准备好没
Are you ready?
你知道 这…
You know, this is, um...
听起来很疯狂 但我觉得生病
It's gonna sound crazy, but I think that maybe getting sick
可能是注定的
happened for a reason, you know?
我不认为我能健康地退役
I don't think I could've walked away healthy.
在这儿
Look, right here.
你永远都会是棒球手
You'll always be a baseball player.
我凭实力拿到的
I got it fair and square.
但这不是你的全部
But it's not all you are.
也不是我爱你的原因
It's not why I fell in love with you.
-不是吗  -不是
No?  No.
别回头看
Don't look back.
记得吗
Remember?
这就是我们所需的
This is all we need.
-好吗  -好
Right?  Yeah.
好的
Yeah.
你知道我的吻有魔力吗
You know my kiss is magic?
真的吗
Oh, really?
是的 如果我们亲吻 你就会痊愈
Yep. If we kiss, you'll be healed.
哇哦
Wow.
喂
Ew, guys.
你们知道我们在这吧
You know we're here, right?
好吧
Okay.
-我好爱你哦  -行吧
"Oh, I love you so much." All right.
-气氛被毁了  -结束了
Ruined it.  Done.
你毁了这一刻
You ruined the moment.
你要付出代价
Now you're gonna pay.
-肉麻死了  -不 爸爸 别过来
So cringe.  No, Dad. Don't do it, don't do it.
-求你了  -你们就不能
Please, no. Could you at least wait
等我们走了再腻歪吗
until we're gone?
爸
Dad?
爸 求你了 不要
Dad, no! Please, no!
你抓不到我们
You can't catch us.
You can't catch us! You can't catch us!
艾略特是我的
Elliot's mine!
-别让他跑了  -来吧 你抓不到我们
Don't let him go.  Come on! You can't catch us!
教师需要实施后门策略
Teachers need to implement backdoor strategies
因为患有多动症的学生和多愁善感的孩子
because students with ADHD and deeply feeling kids
很容易受到感官刺激的影响
can be easily overwhelmed by sensory stimulation,
他们情绪失调时 可能会自闭
and they may shut down when emotionally dysregulated.
在焦虑和课堂表现中
Kids who are struggling with anxiety
挣扎的孩子
and inclass performance...
他们倾向于…
...they're inclined to...
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's the matter?
你不想游泳吗
You don't want to swim? Hmm?
胆小猫
Pussy.
雷 你吓到我了
Ray, you scared me.
他本赛季的第27支全垒打
His 27th home run this season,
观众完全回到了比赛中
and the crowd is fully back in the game.
我们说过很多次 一棒足以定乾坤
So many times, we talk about how momentum can change with one swing of the bat.
一次投球 一场比赛
One pitch, one play...
你全身湿透了
You're all wet.
你刚才在外面吗
Were you outside a minute ago?
没有
No.
我刚睡着了
I think I just fell asleep.
我想为了安全起见 应该装一个泳池盖布
I think we should put in a pool cover just to be safe.
我们还需要检查一下灯
And we need to check out the lights.
好的 没问题
Yeah... Yeah, for sure.
没事吧
Everything okay?
没事 睡觉吧
Yeah. Yeah. Go back to sleep.
妈妈 爸爸
Mom! Dad!
快来看
Come look!
他可能掉下去吓到了
He probably fell in and got scared.
他饿了就会回来的 好吗
Well, he... He'll come back when he's hungry, huh?
我们必须找到他
We have to find him.
我们会去找的
Yeah, that's... We'll go look for him.
我们会找到他的
We'll find him.
没事的 艾利 他会回来的
It's okay, Ellie. He'll come back.
-西达  -过来 西达
Cider. Come here, Cider.
快来 咪咪
Come on, puss.
西达 你去哪了
Cider, where'd you go?
西达
Cider?
伊西 你看过下面了吗
Izzy, did you look down there?
我没看那里
No, I didn't check there.
快来 咪咪
Here, puss.
他可能在这棵树上
Maybe he's up in this tree?
快出来 西达
Come here, Cider.
西达
Cider.
Cider!
你们在屋里找过没
You guys looked inside the house?
-找过  -快出来 咪咪
Yeah. Come here, buddy!
不过没去楼上 你去楼上看了吗
Not upstairs, though. Did you look upstairs?
又问 我发誓 我去楼上找过了
Again? I promise you, I already checked upstairs.
西达
Cider!
过来 西达
Here, Cider.
快来 西达
Come on, Cider.
西达
Cider!
Cider.
西达
想吃东西吗
Want some food?
来吧 西达
Come on, Cider.
加油 使劲
Come on, put your back into it.
我们得把它卷起来 裹紧
We gotta roll it up, make it tight,
这样我们拉开时就很干净整洁
so when we roll it back out, it's all clean and nice.
继续转动 一圈一圈来
Keep cranking. One turn at a time.
-我在努力了  -加油
I'm trying.  Come on.
继续 不要停 继续
Keep going. You strike out, you keep going.
没问题吧
Isn't that right? Yeah.
别放弃 这才是关键
Don't give up. That's the key.
这是最重要的一点 来吧 加油
That's the only thing that matters. Let's go, come on.
干得好 快成功了
Good job. Little wins.
继续加油
Here we go. Come on.
现在对你弟弟好一点
Be nice to your brother right now.
这一切对他来说都不容易
None of this has been easy on him.
继续 继续 干得好
Keep going, keep going. Good job.
好了 看吧
There you go. See?
我知道对你来说也不容易
I know it hasn't been easy on you, either.
不 亲爱的 我没事
Oh, no. Baby, I'm fine.
你不用担心我
I don't want you worrying about me.
什么情况
What is that?
结果怎么样
Um, s... What... What is it?
我从未见过在如此短的时间内
I've never seen such a dramatic improvement
会有如此显著的改善
in such a short time.
我们需要再做些检测
We need to do more tests,
但似乎没有新的病灶了
but it appears there are no new lesions
白色组织也在恢复
and the white tissue is actually improving.
我们按你说的调整了饮食
We started the new diet like you said,
还有水疗
and the water therapy and...
一天两次
Twice a day.
我们有个泳池
We have a pool.
妈妈 我在自习室把作业写完了
Hey, Mom, I finished all my work in study hall.
我能去游泳吗
Can I go swimming?
行 但别一个人去 叫上你爸
Okay, but don't go alone. Ask your dad.
这是进度报告 我…
Here's progress report. I, uh...
你们知道我前段时间被诊断出多发性硬化症
You all know I was diagnosed with MS not too long ago,
时隔不久
a little while back.
-爸  -我在康复中心锻炼
Dad?  I've been able to work out in rehab
在过去的时间里一直与病魔抗争
and been getting back at it for the last little while
取得了相当不错的成效
and I've made a lot of strides that I'm proud of.
我觉得我能展示一下
I think that I can show you,
证明我的水平还在
demonstrate my ability is still at a level that
我很快就能重返战场
I'd be able to make an impact on a team rather quickly.
嘿
Hey, pal.
能帮我个忙吗
Can you help me out with something?
可以
Yeah.
你能装上25磅的吗
Can you throw on a 25?
你录像干什么
What are you doing with the camera?
帮助我训练
Helps me with my training.
你能和我一起潜水找硬币吗
Can you dive for coins with me?
妈妈不让我一个人游泳
Mom says I can't swim alone.
行
Yeah, um...
好的 给我一枚硬币
Yeah. Hey, hand me one of those coins.
你得答应我
You gotta promise me
待在浅水区 好吗
you're gonna stay in the shallow end. Okay?
好的
Okay.
帮我把它扔进泳池
Throw this one in the pool for me.
我会来找的 好吗
And I'll come find it. Okay?
好了
All right.
嘿 老爸
Hey, Dad.
你好
Hello?
我一口气全拿到了
I got 'em all in one breath.
伊西 这不好玩
Izzy? It's not funny.
伊西
Izzy?
我知道是你
I know that's you.
我会留着这些硬币
I'm keeping the money.
好吧 我要潜下去了
Okay, I'm going under.
你好
Hello?
你能听见吗
Can you hear me?
我需要帮助
I need help.
我在找我妈妈
I'm looking for my mom.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是丽贝卡·萨默斯
My name is Rebecca Summers.
我找到了你的玩具
I found your toy.
放开我
Let go of me!
救命
Help!
妈
Mom.
外面有人吗
Is someone out here?
艾利 你确定吗
Ellie, are you sure?
她叫丽贝卡
Her name is Rebecca.
她说她在找她妈妈
She said she was looking for her mom.
可能只是个小孩偷偷溜进来了而已
It was probably just a kid who snuck over the gate. That's all.
反正我们已经装锁了
Anyway, we have a lock on it now, so...
我没看到外面有人
I didn't see anyone out there.
也许他在装模作样
Maybe he's pretending.
因为他还没有真正的朋友
'Cause he doesn't have any real friends yet.
还记得他和宠物壁虎还是蜥蜴什么的说话吗
Remember he talked to that pet gecko or lizard, or whatever?
他那时才五岁
He was five.
但他在它死后 还是说了好几个月的话
Yeah, but he talked to him for months after he died.
他会交朋友的
He's gonna make friends. He just...
他只是需要时间
It just takes him time.
是啊 我今天晚点会去他的训练场
Yeah. I'm going to his practice later today.
也许能帮孩子们打破僵局
So, maybe that'll help, like, break the ice with the kids.
嗯
Yeah.
你也该去 因为你在的时候
You should come, 'cause he always plays better
他总能表现得更好 更像自己
when you're there. He's more himself.
嗯
Hmm.
也许我们该邀请队伍过来
Maybe we should have the team over.
-搞搞烧烤之类  -好啊
You know, for a cookout or something?  Yes.
这主意不错
That's a great idea.
就像泳池派对
Yeah, like a pool party.
所以我才娶你当老婆 你是个天才
That's why I married you, because you're a genius.
邀请你的同事 朋友之类的
Invite your coworkers, friends, whoever.
来见见沃勒一家 对吧
Just "Meet the Wallers," right?
-听起来很棒  -我能邀请朋友吗
Sounds great. Can I invite some friends?
当然 邀请谁都行 这是个好主意
Yes, invite whoever you want. It's a great idea.
我们应该邀请所有认识的人
We should invite everybody you know.
-我们是热情好客的家庭  -别说了
We're a welcoming family. Stop.
你觉得我们的泳池能容纳多少人
How many people you think we can fit in the pool?
我们现在是泳池家庭
We're the pool family now.
好了 往前传
All right. Get in front of it.
很好 传过去
Good. Move it around.
就这样 传过去 传过去
There you go, in front of it, in front of it.
就是这样
It's all right. It's all right.
往前面传
Get in front of it. In front of it.
拜托 打起精神
Come on, wake up, man.
动作快点
Let's hustle. Let's hustle, boys.
你知道棒球是什么吧
You know what baseball is, right?
就是一根棍子 一个球
It's a stick and a ball
和一群穿着长袜的人
and a bunch of guys wearing long socks.
也是比赛
It's play.
为什么对爸爸和伊西来说这么容易
How come it's so easy for Dad and Izzy?
并非如此
It's not.
每个人都有害怕的事物
Everyone's scared of something.
伊西以前讨厌上幼儿园
Izzy used to hate drop-off in kindergarten.
我每天都会在教室窗外等着
Every day, I'd wait outside until I saw her
直到看到她 她会给我打招呼
in the classroom window, and she'd give me the signal.
-告诉他 伊西  -就是这样
Show him, Iz. There we go!
做得好
Good job, good job.
可以上场了
Green light to swing.
等球 孩子们
Wait for the ball, boys!
快点 快点
Come on, come on!
-他来了  -教练 抱歉我来迟了
Hey, there he is. Hey, Coach. Sorry I'm late.
-好啊 各位  -好啊
Hey, guys. Hey.
好了
All right.
你能行的
You got this.
孩子们 这是艾略特的爸爸
Hey, boys, this is Elliot's dad.
他以前是酿酒人队的三垒手
He's a former Brewers third baseman,
他是来把你们变成全明星击球手的
and he's here to turn you into allstar hitters.
你能行的 心态放松
You got this. You got this. Nice and easy.
你得盯着球 别光想着挥棒
You gotta follow through the ball. Don't just, like, check swing.
-这就对了  -太棒了
There you go.  Yes! Nice!
很好 直飞中线 不错
All right. Line drive up the middle. There you go.
传球 传球
All right, move it around, move it around.
你腰弯得太低了
You're bent way over at the waist, right?
你要带动身体
And you turn out with your body.
别只用手击球 要动用你的身体
Don't hit it with your hands. You turn out with your body.
-做得好  -好样的
All right. Good job. There you go!
掌握住技巧 做得很好
Way to get on top of it. Good job.
雷 那是我儿子 阿泰
Oh, hey, Ray, that's my son, Ty.
留点心 他技术不错
Yeah, keep an eye. He's got good mechanics.
好的 阿泰 看看你的本事
All right, Ty. Let's see what you got.
就是这样
There you go.
太棒了 阿泰
Yes, Ty! Yes!
-打得好  -我不会让你失望的 老爸
Good swing. Good hit. Yeah, I got you, Dad.
-很棒  -谢谢 沃勒先生
Good job. Thanks, Mr. Waller.
艾利 准备好了吗
All right, El, you ready?
加油 艾利
Go, Ellie!
-开始吧  -嘿 祝你好运
All right, let's go. Hey. Good luck out there, man.
你没问题的
You got this.
好样的 阿泰
Way to go. Good job, Ty.
嘿 艾利
Hey, Ellie.
好了 艾略特
All right, Elliot.
来吧 你可以的
All right, come on. You got this.
你能行的 艾略特
You got it, Elliot.
对了 漂亮
There you go. Nice! Nice going.
就是这样 好样的
There you go. All right. Good job.
真棒 艾略特
Yes, Elliot. All right.
这就是盯球的作用
That's what stepping into the ball does.
盯好了球 就能一击必中
You go after it and you get it.
好样的 真棒
Good job. Way to go.
试试球场的另一边
Try for the other side of the field. Way to go.
我们能做好的 别担心
We'll work on it. Don't worry about it.
雷 你想打几棒吗
Hey, Ray, you want to take some?
如果你准备好了的话
I mean, if you're up for it.
-来吗  -当然啦
Yeah? Sure, right?
打几棒 没问题的
Take a couple. I'll be fine.
好的 准备好 孩子们
All right. All right, get ready, boys! Get ready!
好的
All right.
准备好没
Okay, you ready?
你们都准备好没
You guys ready out there?
屈膝 屈膝
Bend your knees. Bend your knees.
手下留情啊
Take it easy on me.
我有段时间没打球了
I haven't swung in a while.
等下 我放松下身体
All right, hold on. Let me loosen up real quick.
-好的 下一球  -等我… 好的
Okay, okay. Next one. Just let me... Yeah.
爸
Dad?
你没事吧 老大
You okay, boss?
雷 你还好吗
Ray? You okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
我没事 继续吧
I'm good. Let's keep going.
-好的  -我没事
Okay. I'm good. I'm good.
靠
Shit.
接着扔吧
Why don't you throw that again?
行
All right.
天啊
Oh, my God!
看到没 就该这样击球
See, boys, that's how you hit a ball.
就该这样打
That's how you hit it, man.
你知道规矩 呆在家里 10点前睡觉
You know the deal. Stay in the house, bed by 10:00.
-我们吃完饭就回来  -嗯
We'll be back after dinner.  Mmhmm.
别让我后悔没找保姆
Don't make me regret not getting a sitter.
好 知道了
Yeah, okay, I know.
雷 准备好没
Ray, you ready?
我们得走了
We gotta go.
马上会有人过来 不是什么大事
Hey, someone's coming over in a minute. It's not a big deal.
好的
Okay.
是为了游泳队的事
It's for the swim team.
好的
Okay.
如果你告诉妈妈
If you tell Mom,
我就往你鱼缸里放肥皂
I'm gonna put a Tide POD in your fish tank.
好的
Okay.
马可
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
马可
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
马可 马可
Marco. Marco.
波罗
Polo.
你耍赖 你睁眼了
You're cheating. You opened your eyes.
你湿发的样子很好看
I mean, you look great with your hair wet.
该你说“波罗”了
You're supposed to say "Polo."
-波罗  -别闹
Polo.   Stop.
好了 马可
Okay. Marco.
波罗
Polo.
有鱼出水了
Fish out of water.
没有
Nope.
马可
Marco.
快点 你得回应
Come on. You have to say something back.
波罗
Polo.
马可
Marco.
波罗
Polo.
马可
Marco?
罗尼 拜托别闹了 马可
Ronin, stop, please. Marco.
波罗
Polo.
我听见了
I hear you.
你就在这
You're right there.
马可
Marco. Come on.
来吧
Come on.
抓到你了 不
Got you. No!
波罗
Polo.
罗尼 你死定了
Ronin, you're dead.
找到你了
I got you.
你为什么不说“有鱼出水”
Wait, why didn't you call "fish out of water"?
-伊西  -我的天
Izzy?  Oh, my God.
嘿
Hey.
伊西
Izzy?
伊西 你没事吧
Izzy, you okay?
嘿 回答我
Hey, hey, hey. Talk to me.
水下有东西 有东西抓我
Something was down there. Something grabbed me.
-有东西抓你  -你没在下面吗
Something grabbed you?  Were you not down there?
没有 听着 没事的 我在这呢
No. Look, look, it's okay. Look, I'm right here.
我什么都没看见
I didn't see anything.
你只在水下呆了几秒钟
You were only down there for a couple seconds.
可能是你的脚卡在泳池清洁器里了
Maybe your foot got stuck in the pool cleaner.
-是不是  -我不知道 可能吧
Did it?  I... I don't know. Maybe.
没事的 没事的
It's okay, all right? It's okay.
下面什么都没有
There's nothing there.
伊西
Izzy!
-爸妈回家了  -糟糕
Mom and Dad are home! Shit. Oh, shit.
我没跟爸妈说你会来
I didn't tell my parents you were coming over.
对不起 你得拿上东西
I'm sorry. You gotta grab your stuff
-从后门离开  -好的
and get out the back gate.  All right.
谢谢你邀请我过来
Well, thanks for inviting me over.
好的 那周六见
All right, great. I'll catch you on Saturday?
周六吗
Uh, Saturday?
泳池派对
The pool party.
-哦 好的  -好
Oh. Yeah.  All right.
门打不开
The gate won't open.
（沃勒家族泳池派对 走这边）
伊西
Izzy.
我知道昨晚有东西吓到你了
I know something scared you last night.
我看到你从水里出来的样子
I saw the way you got out of the water.
走开
Go away.
告诉我
Tell me.
不然我告诉爸妈你男朋友来过
Or I'm gonna tell Mom and Dad your boyfriend was here.
你看到东西了 对吗
You saw something, didn't you?
没有
No.
我的腿被泳池清洁器卡住了而已
My leg just got caught in the pool cleaner.
你说谎 我看得出来
You're lying. I can tell.
别说了
Stop.
自从我们搬到这里 生活好了许多
Things have been better since we moved here.
我是说 爸爸更健康了
I mean, Dad's healthier.
妈妈也开心了
Mom's happy.
你想吓坏他们 然后再次搬家吗
Do you want to freak them out just so we have to move again?
哪种说法更有意义
What makes more sense,
泳池在帮我们 还是泳池在闹鬼
that the pool's helping us or that it's haunted?
如果两者都有呢
What if it's both?
我回来啦
Hey, I'm back!
别多嘴
Keep your mouth shut.
嘿 你们俩人呢
Hey. Where are you two?
反正也没人会相信我们
No one's gonna believe us anyway.
来了 妈妈 我来帮你
Coming, Mom. I can help.
没事吧
Everything okay?
是的 妈妈 没事
Yeah, Mom. Everything's fine.
该死
Oh, shit.
见到你们太好了
It's so nice to meet you guys.
你真的不必这么客气
I mean, you really didn't have to bring that.
开玩笑 你在招待整个街坊
Are you kidding? You're hosting the entire neighborhood.
-谢谢  -不客气
Thank you.  Of course.
沃勒先生在吗
Uh, is Mr. Waller here?
在的 他在后面
Oh, yeah. He's out back.
你们可以去打招呼
Youyou guys can go say hi.
嘿 天啊 这房子太赞了
Hey. Oh, my God, the house looks great.
哇瑟
Oh, wow.
我做了松软的朗姆酒蛋糕
I made my jiggly rum cake.
哇
Wow.
但不是给孩子们吃的
But this is not for the kids. Okay?
我放了很多摩根船长朗姆酒
There's enough Captain Morgan in here
足以让菲尔醉到穿丁字裤
to get Phil into his famous Bermuda Gstring.
你看上去好多了
You seem to be doing a lot better, man.
-谢谢  -我从没见过
Thank you.  I don't think I've ever seen
这么有力的击球
anybody hit a ball that hard.
见到我经纪人的时候 你可以告诉他
Tell my agent that when you see him.
他曾是埃文·朗格利亚 马可·特谢拉的代理人
Yeah, he used to rep Evan Longoria, Mark Teixeira.
-他代理过很多优秀选手  -不会吧
He repped a lot of good people.  No shit.
-真的  -我很想让阿泰见见他
Yeah.  You know, I'd love for Ty to meet him.
好啊 也许我能叫他
Yeah, sure. Maybe I can get him
-来趟训练场  -太阳出来喜洋洋咯
to come to practice. Sun's out, guns out.
准备好没 下水吧
You ready? Let's go. Coming in.
他昨晚过来游泳了
Yeah, so he... He came over for a swim last night.
挺好玩的
Um, it was cool.
但他吻了我
But, uh, he... He kissed me.
闭嘴吧 别吹牛了
Shut up. No, he didn't.
我真觉得他是基督徒反而更性感
But I... I actually think it's hotter that he's Christian.
真的吗
Really?
真的 有种禁欲感
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. It's, like, forbidden.
伊西 我给你拿了这个
Hey, Izzy, I got this for you.
-你还好吗  -还好
You all right? Yeah.
咋啦
What?
没什么 我们只是…
Nothing. We were just...
-我们在说该去游泳了  -我们去游会儿泳
We were saying we should go for a swim.  We're gonna go for a swim.
-是的  -我们要去水里玩
Yeah.  We're gonna head out to the water.
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
我不去了 谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
-确定吗 好吧  -是的
You sure? All right.  Yeah.
孩子们一定很喜欢这个泳池
The kids must love the pool.
你会游泳吗
Do you swim?
我爸爸是海军
Oh, my dad was Navy.
我还没学走路 就先学潜水了
I was doing dive drills before I could walk.
你该看看她看到这栋房子时
Oh. Well, you should have seen her eyes light up
两眼发光的样子
when she saw this place.
我看得出你经常办招待
I can tell that you're used to hosting.
雷比赛的时候我们经常搬家
Well, we moved so much when Ray was playing.
很高兴明年能见到一些熟人
It's just nice to meet people you might actually know next year.
我们会熟络的
You're gonna know us.
不管你喜不喜欢 这是一年一度的活动
This is an annual event, like it or not.
你今天带泳衣了吗
And did you bring your suit today?
-带了 我已经穿上了  -好的
I did. I'm wearing it already.  Okay, good.
我已经25年没穿过泳衣了
I haven't had a suit in 25 years.
嘿 艾利
Hey, El!
艾利
El!
你在哪里 我们下水玩吧
Where are you? Let's get in the pool.
-沃勒先生  -嘿
Mr. Waller?  Hey.
嘿 艾利
Hey, El!
能给我签个名吗
Will you sign this for me?
我昨晚找了一个小时才找到
It took me like an hour to find it last night.
当然可以
Yeah, of course.
-非常感谢  -不客气
Thank you so much.  Yeah.
给
There you go.
-好好保存  -我会的
Now hold on to that.  I will.
总有一天会很有价值的
It's gonna be worth something someday.
-好  -好的
Yeah.  Yeah.
-嘿  -怎么了
Hey.  Yeah?
史莱克觉得他称霸泳池
Steroid Shrek over here thinks he owns the damn pool.
你觉得我们能干倒他吗
Think we can take him?
我无敌
Yeah, I got you, man!
-我们能行的  -好的
All right, we got this, okay?  Yeah. All right.
-我们上  -好
Let's go. Come on.  Okay.
准备好没 大联盟
You ready, Big League?
好样的
Nice, buddy.
放倒他们 麦克
Get 'em, Mikey!
我们在修泳池的时候
You know, when we were fixing up the pool,
他们说大概有15年没用过了
they said it hadn't been used in probably 15 years.
也许更久
Maybe longer.
很奇怪 不是吗
It's weird, right?
不 我不清楚
No. No, I don't know.
也许他们不喜欢游泳
Maybe they weren't pool people.
-凯  -嗯
Kay?  Hmm?
好吧 你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
这是你的新家
You know, this is your new home,
我实在不想说些话来…
and II didn't want to say anything that would taint your ...
扫你的兴
Your feelings about this house.
拜托 我们都买下好几个月了 到底怎么回事
Come on, we closed months ago. What is it?
加油 阿泰 用你的核心力量
Get it, buddy. Yeah. Ty, use your core.
上 用核心力量 阿泰
Let's go! Use your core, Ty.
就是这样 身体前倾
There you go. Lean forward a little bit.
-就是这样  -往前倾
Yeah. That's it.  Lean forward.
用胳膊 往下 麦克
Use your arms. Your arms. Going down, Mikey.
我发誓 我不知道就是这栋房子
I swear, I had no idea that this was the same house
等我朋友告诉我时 你已经搬进来了
until my friend told me after you'd already moved in.
我本想告诉你 但你看起来如此开心
And I was gonna tell you, but you seemed so happy here. And I...
我不想泼你冷水
I didn't want to put any poo in the pudding.
很有可能
It... It's very possible
以前住在这里的人…
that the people that lived here before, that they...
他们喜欢这个街区 想要一个好的学区
You know, they liked the neighborhood, and they wanted the good school district,
但他们不喜欢使用泳池
but they didn't feel comfortable using the pool
因为某些传言
because of certain alleged events.
传言
Alleged events?
是的 我…
Yeah, I...
我记不太清了
You know, I don't remember much about it.
传言有一个小女孩
Just there were these stories about this little girl who...
来自哈罗德霍尔特高中
Uh, from Harold Holt...
她在这里淹死了
and she drowned here.
我知道 这是场悲剧
I know, it's just... Oh, it is a tragedy.
我不知道为什么有人会因此
You know, I mean, I don't know why that would make
不想用这么完美的泳池
someone not want to use a perfectly good swimming pool,
但你知道吗
but you know what?
人们都很迷信
People are... They're superstitious.
不是吗
Aren't they, really?
那个小女孩是不是叫丽贝卡
Was the little girl's name Rebecca?
慢着 你怎么知道
Wait. How did you know that?
好的 继续推
Okay, keep pushing.
加油 打倒他们
Let's go. Let's take 'em down.
加油 阿泰
Come on, Ty.
-别放弃 用腿  -我们上
Don't give up. Use your legs. Let's go.
加油 阿泰 继续
Come on, Ty. Keep going.
用腿 你能行的 继续推
Use your legs, Ty. You got him. Keep pushing.
我们上
Let's go now.
别放弃 打败他 麦克
Don't give up. Get him, Mikey.
-就是这样  -你要下去了
That's it, buddy. You're going down!
我们赢啦
Let's go! We won!
赢啦
Let's go!
我们做到了 沃勒先生
We did it, Mr. Waller!
你可以放开我了
All right, you can let go now.
沃勒先生 沃勒先生
Mr. Waller. Mr. Waller.
放手 嘿
Hey, let go. Hey!
沃勒先生 请你放手
Mr. Waller, please let go.
你抓着我的腿 沃勒先生
You've got my legs, Mr. Waller.
放手 放手
Let go! Let go!
沃勒先生
Mr. Waller.
你抓着我的腿呢 住手
You're grabbing on my legs. Stop.
放手 沃勒先生
Let go! Mr. Waller!
沃勒先生
Mr. Waller...
放手
Let go!
妈
Mom!
嘿 阿泰
Hey, Ty.
阿泰
Ty.
-你看到阿泰了吗  -妈 妈
Baby, you seen Ty? Mom! Mom!
妈 泳池出事了
Mom. Outside in the pool.
天啊 阿泰
Oh, my God. Ty!
天呐
Oh, my...
-阿泰  -快让开
Ty?  Out of the way! Out of the way!
阿泰 出什么事了
Ty! What happened?
帮帮我 快来人帮忙
Help me! Someone help!
-给我  -拉他上来
Give him to me. Get him out.
拉到岸上
Pull him over the edge.
快打电话求救
Someone call for help!
-妈 快看 是爸爸  -让开
Mom, look! It's Dad! Move!
-阿泰 快呼吸  -没事的
Ty, breathe. Breathe. It's okay. It's okay.
-我来  -快呼吸 发生了什么
I got him.  Come on, breathe, breathe. What happened?
怎么回事
What happened?
到底怎么回事
What the hell happened?
快打电话求救
Someone call for help.
打911
Call 911!
-打电话求救 -雷 雷
Someone call for help. Ray. Ray.
怎么回事 阿泰
What happened, Ty?
爸 爸
Dad? Dad?
-没事了  -好的
You're okay. Okay.
-抓着我的手  -没事了
Yeah, just hold on to my arm.  It's okay. It's okay.
好了 扶他进屋
Okay. Let's get him inside.
-一 二…  -好了 没事了
Okay, one, two...  It's okay. You're okay.
阿泰说他死不松手
Ty said he wouldn't let go.
不 教练 你知道疾病会侵袭他的神经系统
No, Coach, you know the disease attacks his nervous system.
他也差点淹死了
I mean... No. He nearly drowned, too.
我们不会起诉的 警官
We're not gonna press charges, Officer.
我们没事
We're fine.
嘿 伊芙 我…
Hey, Eve, I just...
我觉得雷不该再来训练场了
I don't think Ray should come to practice anymore.
真的很对不起
Look, I'm so sorry.
你听到他说的了吗
Do you hear what he's saying?
别再靠近我的家人
Don't come near our family again.
-快点 我们走  -等等
Come on, let's go. Let's go. Wait. Wait.
-站住  -赶紧…
Stop, stop. Stop.  Here, just put the...
-停下  -上车
Stop! God, wait.  Get in the car.
我们要去哪儿
Wait. Where are we going?
我不知道 反正不能待在这
I don't know. Just not here.
那个泳池有问题
There's something wrong with that pool.
伊芙 泳池没有问题
Eve, there's nothing wrong with the pool.
泳池很好
The pool's fine.
那个泳池是我一生中最棒的东西
The pool's the greatest thing to ever happen to me.
听着 亲爱的 这次不一样
Look... Listen. I mean, honey, it would be different this time.
这次会大不相同 我们不必做同样的牺…
It would be so different. We wouldn't have to make the same sacri...
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你今天差点淹死
You almost drowned today.
那个小男孩差点淹死
That little boy almost drowned.
好了
All right.
爸
Dad?
-爸 停下  -妈 怎么回事
Dad, stop. Mom, what's going on?
停车
Stop the car.
-妈 做点什么  -我不知该怎么办
Mom, do something.  I don't know what to do.
他在呼吸吗
Is he breathing?
-发生了什么  -他不能呼吸了
What is happening? Please! He can't breathe!
-咳出来  -天呐
Cough it out.  Oh, my God.
爸 快把他扶下车
Dad. Get him out of the car!
不不 他现在稳定了 但我…
No, no, no, he's stable now, but I...
我从没见过他这样
I've never seen him like this before.
感觉就像有东西从内部攻击他
It was like something was attacking him from the inside.
我知道这种症状很可怕
Look, I know these episodes are frightening.
我可以让他周二过来
I can have him come in on Tuesday
再进行一轮检测 但同时
for another round of tests, but in the meantime,
让他好好休养
just let him rest and recover.
伊芙
Eve.
对不起 我不知道怎么回事
I'm sorry. I don't know what's happening.
-没关系  -我不是故意伤害那个男孩的
It's okay.  I didn't mean to hurt that boy.
你不必多说
You don't have to talk.
我们会让你稳定下来
We'll just get you stable and just...
我们会想办法的
We'll figure out what to do.
只需要再来一次 一次就好
It's just one more time. It's just one more.
我只需要再来一次
I just need one more time.
你可以带我去泳池 我只需再下一次水
You can carry me into the pool. I just need to get in one more time.
在深水里的感觉很棒
It's so cool in the deep water.
让人无法自拔
It's so cool in the deep.
我跟他说今晚可以睡在这
I told him he could sleep here tonight.
你记得你爸说过在你出生的时候
You know your dad talks about being at bat
他在球场上忽然感觉浑身充满了力量吗
and feeling this rush of strength when you were born?
我当时22岁 在医院里被陌生人围着
I was 22 in a hospital surrounded by strangers, and...
我感觉自己很孤独
And I felt totally alone.
但我没…
And I didn't...
我没想过我有力气生孩子
And I didn't think I could keep pushing.
我没想过我能…
I didn't think I would... I didn't...
我没想过我能当个好妈妈
I didn't think I would be a good mom.
我只想放弃
And I just wanted to give up.
你一定感觉到了我有多害怕
And you must have felt how scared I was.
因为突然间 你就出生了
Because suddenly, there you were.
我不再孤独
And I wasn't alone anymore.
只要我们拥有彼此 就永远不会孤独
We're never alone if we have each other.
我不会让我们出事的 好吗
I'm not gonna let anything bad happen to us, okay?
好的
Okay.
嗨 伊芙 很抱歉你的派对不欢而散
Hi, Eve. I'm sorry your party ended on a sour note,
但只要给点时间 大家都会忘记的
but you give people time and they're gonna forget all about it.
凯 我不是为了这件事
Kay, it's not that. It's...
你觉得你是个思想开放的人吗
Would you consider yourself an open-minded person?
我想是的
Yeah, I like to think so.
为什么这么问
Why are you asking?
不只是丽贝卡
It wasn't just Rebecca.
如果再往前查询 你会发现
If you go back, there's more people
还有很多住在这里的人失踪了
who lived at the house who just went missing.
我需要知道这是怎么回事
I need to know what's going on.
伊芙 我发誓我把知道的都告诉你了
Eve, I swear I told you everything I knew at the house.
我也不清楚是怎么回事
I don't know anything about this.
-告诉我 你要我怎么帮你  -萨默斯一家住在附近吗
Just tell me what I can do to help.  Does the Summers family live nearby?
你好
Hi.
我叫伊芙·沃勒
My name is Eve Waller.
我昨天试着打给你
I tried to call you yesterday.
我想我家住在你的老房子里
I think my family lives in your old house.
带泳池那个
With the pool?
哦 是的
Oh. Yes.
请进
Come in.
那是汤马斯
That's Thomas.
美国国际开发署驻华盛顿大使
USAID ambassador in Washington.
在难民危机期间 他在苏丹的工作拯救了数千人
His work in Sudan saved thousands during the refugee crisis.
你儿子吗
Your son?
对 我的小骄傲
Yeah. My pride and joy.
他供养了这个漂亮的房子
He's responsible for this beautiful home.
不过他很少来看我
Though he doesn't visit as much as I'd like.
如果你不介意的话 我只能走这么远了
This is about as far as I can make it, if you don't mind.
请坐
Please.
我知道这很奇怪 但我想问问
I know this is strange, but I wanted to ask you about
你住在那栋房子里的事
when you lived at the house.
多么特别的地方
What a special place.
汤米很喜欢那个泳池
Tommy loved that pool.
怎么叫都叫不上岸
I could hardly get him out of the water.
你是不是还有个女儿
Did you have a daughter, too?
没有 只有我和汤马斯
No, it's... It's just Thomas and I.
他写的信美妙至极
Oh, he writes the most wonderful letters.
他在华盛顿
He's in Washington,
做了很多好事
doing so much good.
萨默斯夫人 我不是来惹你心烦的
Mrs. Summers, I'm not here to upset you.
但我不知道还能找谁
But I don't know who else to talk to.
我丈夫病了
My husband was sick,
我们搬进了那栋房子
and we moved into the house,
他身体开始好转
and he started getting better.
我觉得
And I think
是那个泳池让他好转的
the pool made him better.
但我的孩子看见了一些东西
But my kids have seen things.
我也看见了
And so have I.
水里有不好的东西 是不是
There's something bad in the water, isn't there?
你女儿出了什么事
What happened to your daughter?
丽贝卡
To Rebecca?
求你了 我担心我丈夫会出同样的事
Please. I'm worried that the same thing is going to happen to my husband.
你小时候用过许愿池吗
Did you ever use a wishing well as a child?
把硬币扔进水里
Throw a coin in the water
然后用心许愿
and pray with all your heart.
有些水有魔力
Some water is magic.
在建起房子
Before there was a house
或泳池之前
or a pool,
那里有一处泉水
there was a spring in the ground.
我不知道水下是什么
I don't know what's beneath the surface.
也许没有人知道
Maybe no one does.
但我知道它能满足我们内心的愿望
But I know it gives us our deepest desires.
当时的人们发现它的能力后
The people then must have worshipped it
都很崇拜它
when they found out what it could do.
塔玛戈米
Temagami.
深水
The deep water.
塔玛戈米 塔玛戈米
Temagami. Temagami.
那口井有自己的愿望
The well has a wish of its own.
一旦水被唤醒 就会夺走一条生命
Once the water is woken, it will take a life.
必须有人付出代价 水才能不断满足愿望
Someone has to pay so the water can keep giving.
它就这样满足了我的愿望
The way it gave to me.
汤米病得很重
Tommy was so sick.
你再看他现在
And look at him now.
但你女儿发生了什么
But what happened to your daughter?
选丽贝卡
It was...
更合适
better with Rebecca,
选一个不知死神将至的孩子
more humane for a child not to know
更人道一些
what was coming.
妈 救命
Mom! Help!
妈 妈
Mom! Mom!
妈
Mom!
贝基 贝基
Becky? Becky!
妈 妈
Mom! Mom!
救命
Help!
妈 贝基在外面
Mom, Becky's outside!
妈 妈
Mom! Mom!
妈
Mom!
妈 贝基在外面
Mom, Becky's outside!
水把我当作容器
The water used me as a vessel
去完成必须完成的事
to do what must be done.
不用担心你的丈夫
Don't worry about your husband.
他是愿望成真的人
He's the one who gets the wish.
他得到了健康
He gets his health.
我得到了大病初愈的儿子
I got my son back.
这很值得
It'll be worth it.
你会明白的
You'll see.
爱需要牺牲
Love requires sacrifice.
那不是爱
That's not love.
如果得到了回报 那就不叫牺牲
It's not a sacrifice if you get something back.
丽贝卡问你在哪里
Rebecca asked where you were.
她还在找你
She's still looking for you.
你还可以帮我们
You can still help us.
肯定有办法阻止这一切
There has to be some way to stop this.
很快就会结束了
It'll be over soon.
水会再次陷入沉睡
The water will sleep again.
然后
And...
其他人会找到这栋房子
someone else will find the house.
其他需要帮助的人
Someone else who needs its help.
谢谢 罗尼 明天见
Thanks, Ronin. See you tomorrow.
妈妈 爸爸 我们回来了
Hey, Mom, Dad, we're home.
妈
Mom?
爸 我们回来了
Dad, we're home.
她没接电话
She's not answering.
爸爸可能和她在一起
Think Dad might be with her.
我去车库看看
I'm gonna go check the garage.
西达
Cider?
过来 西达
Come here, Cider.
什么
What?
西达
Cider?
没事的 咪咪
It's okay, buddy.
有我在呢
I'm right here.
西达
Cider?
艾略特
Elliot!
艾略特 艾略特
Elliot! Elliot!
妈
Mom.
-伊西 快帮我  -好的
Izzy, help me. Come on. Come on. Okay, okay.
我不知道发生了什么 艾略特掉下去了
I don't know what happened. I don't know... Elliot's down there.
-我只知道…  -进屋去
All I know is that he...  Go in the house.
-报警 快  -好的 我这就去
Call for help. Go!  Okay. Okay, I'm going.
爸
Dad!
Dad?
-爸  -你在这呢
Dad!  There you are.
我一直在找你 伊西
I've been looking for you, Iz.
怎么了
What's the matter?
好的 我打电话报警
Okay, I'm... I'm calling for help.
不准打
Don't do that!
我知道你想让我好起来
I know you want me to get better.
你明白的吧
You understand, don't you?
我们得找人帮忙
We have to get help.
亲爱的 我们已经得到帮助了
Baby, we already got help.
生活对艾略特来说太艰难了
Life is too hard for Elliot.
这样比较好
It's better this way.
不 不
No! No!
救命啊
Help! Help! Help!
马可
Marco.
救命
Help!
快来人 救命啊
Please! Help!
外面有人吗 快报警
Is anyone out there? Call for help!
马可
Marco.
你应该说“波罗”
You're supposed to say "Polo."
你就乖乖呆在这 很快就会结束了
Why don't you stay here, and it'll all be over soon?
艾利
Ellie.
天啊 拜托
Oh, God. Come on.
快醒醒 艾利
Come on, Ellie. Come on.
一 二 三 四 五
One, two, three, four, five.
快醒醒
Come on. Come on.
太迟了
It's too late.
爱需要牺牲
Love requires sacrifice.
雷
Ray.
雷 求你了
Oh, Ray, please.
我们得带他去医院
Please, we need to get him to a hospital, Ray.
他需要你的帮助 看看他
He needs your help. Look at him.
水选择了他
The water chose him.
他爱这个泳池
He loves the pool.
艾略特会永远留在这
Elliot will always be here.
他会永远在这
He'll always be here.
爸
Dad.
有东西控制了你
Something has you.
你必须反抗
You have to fight it.
你们都需要做出牺牲
It's going to take sacrifice,
但你们可以一起建立美好的生活
but you can have a good life together.
我只是想确定这也是你想要的
I just need to know that you want that, too.
求你回来
Please come back.
我也希望那样
I want that, too.
艾略特需要你
Elliot needs you.
雷
Ray?
回来吧
Come back.
Come back. Come back.
伊西 不
Izzy, no. Izzy...
是我
Yeah, it's me.
对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
妈
Mom.
-艾利  -他没事吧
Ellie!  Is he okay?
他有呼吸了 我们得带他离开这
He's breathing. We gotta get him out of here.
来吧 孩子
Come on. Come on, baby.
爸 我们快走
Dad, come on. Let's go.
塔玛戈米
Temagami.
爸
Dad?
天啊 妈
Oh, my God. Mom?
孩子 怎么了
Baby, what's wrong?
-艾略特  -妈 是水
Elliot.  Mom, it's the water.
它不会让他离开的
It's not gonna let him leave.
雷 情况更糟了
Ray, it's... It's getting worse.
扶他起来 伊西 帮我下
Get him up, Izzy. Help me.
必须有人付出代价
Someone has to pay.
爸
Dad?
爸 你要去哪儿
Dad, where are you going?
别回头看
Don't look back.
雷
Ray?
爸
Dad!
艾利
Ellie!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-你没事吧  -我没事
Are you okay?  I'm okay.
我没事
I'm good.
我很好
I'm okay.
爸爸呢
Where's Dad?
我扶你
I got you.
好了
Okay.
嘿 伊芙 孩子们
Hey, Eve, kids.
我不知道结果会如何
I don't know what's gonna come of all this,
但我觉得我还需要证明些东西
but I just feel like I still got something to prove.
你知道
You know, and...
我想让你们感到自豪
I want to make you proud.
棒球对我来说一直很容易
Baseball's always just come easy to me.
但其他事情就不轻松了
And... the other stuff, not so much.
所以…
So...
我想我只是…
I guess I just...
希望有更好的办法
wish I knew a better way
让你们知道你们对我有多重要
to let you know how much you mean to me.
爱你们
Love you.
这是你的吗
This yours?
我们依然可以卖掉房子
You know, we could still sell the house.
我们可以去任何地方
I mean, we could go anywhere.
但这种事会发生在其他人身上
But then it's going to happen to someone else, isn't it?
爸爸不会希望那样的
Dad wouldn't want that.
《暗泳》